TOMOMI OKI

My passion lies in using my creativity to build tools for the digital future. My experiences in the past years at production set-up have allowed me to understand the importance of delivering commercially viable products and maintaining quality at its best. Along the way, skills that I have learnt enable me to work collaboratively in a team environment, clearly communicate ideas to people and thrive under pressure.

212/101 Grattan st, Carlton VIC 3053

2 0433 006 651

■ tomomioki@outlook.com

https://github.com/okichan/ https://www.linkedin.com/in/tomomi-oki-parsons/

KEY SKILLS & COMPETENCIES

WEB DEVELOPMENT & DESIGN

- Experience in front-end technologies: HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, React.js, Bootstrap, Flexbox Grid
- Experience in back-end technologies: Ruby on Rails, Node.js, Express.js, SQLite, PostrgreSQL, MongoDB
- Experience in using the following tools: JIRA, GitHub, Bitbucket, TortoiseSVN, Trello and Heroku
- Strong capabilities in producing a web app from concept, design to production by designing user experience (UX) elements such as hand drawn/high fidelity wireframes, user flow diagrams and database schema design to guide the build process

MARKETING RESEARCH

- Proficient in extracting data with MS SQL for supporting business decision.
- Experience in programming Java based software in agile environment.
- Experience in building online survey using HTML, CSS and XML.
- Strong capabilities in data stimulation and user interface design using MS Excel formulas and macros.
- Strong ability to design question structure and survey flow, contribute to issues related to survey design.

CUSTOMER SUPPORT/ QUALITY CONTROL

- Demonstrated attention to detail by performing routine inspections, following product quality control procedures, and proofreading survey reports.
- Experience in providing customer support in busy call centre environments for mystery shopping industry.
- Proven ability in providing accurate solutions and advice in a timely and professional manner via email.

OTHER

- Excellent analytical and practical problem solving skills demonstrated via academic and professional experience.
- Good communication skills in writing and conversing in English and Japanese.
- High level of comfort conducting business in a diverse range of cultures.

PERSONAL PROJECT HIGHLIGHTS

Tanto Management system

A real-world collaboration project with a high-end Japanese knife store.

https://mct-project-t3demo.netlify.com Technologies used:

React.js, Bootstrap, Netlify

Repository:

https://github.com/okichan/majo r-project-term3

Wordsworth – Two-sided Market Project

An Airtasker-like translation portal for office workers and translators.

https://wordsworth.herokuapp.c

Technologies used: Ruby on Rails, Bootstrap, Heroku

Repository:

https://github.com/okichan/word sworth

Personal Portfolio

My first personal portfolio web page.

http://tomomioki.netlify.com/ Technologies used: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript

Repository:

https://github.com/okichan/portf olio v2

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End developer intern

Serraview (2018 Feb)

https://serraview.com

Serraview is a cloud-based software company that provides space optimisation solutions. Their key service includes providing real-time data such as desk occupancy rate and peak people value to assist strategic control of clients' workspace.

- Worked on front-end development using Angluar4 under supervision of senior developer
- Attended 2-week sprint meeting, daily stand-up

Senior Production Set-up Officer

GBW (2015 - 2016)

http://www.gbw.solutions

GBW is a global Customer Experience and Mystery Shopping Agency that specialises in collecting customers' feedback for some of the world's largest brands. Their mission is to help clients track and improve customer experience by using a range of advanced products and services to ensure insights are accurate, current and applicable.

- Provided survey structure expertise to best suit each client's requirements
- Provided estimated cost for each project's start-up

- Investigated data and provided analytical findings for business decision purposes
- Attended kick-off meetings, provided feasibility recommendations

Production Set-up Officer

GBW (2007 - 2015)

- Created unique identification number associated to each mystery shopping projects, and maintained them throughout the survey lifecycle
- Programmed back-end survey behaviour and built user interface in the formats of pdf and website
- Created client reports in designated layouts and colour schemes from their mock-up

Customer Support/ Quality Control Officer

GBW (2007)

- Quality control each report sent from mystery shoppers and spot contradictions, detect potential fraud
- Helpdesk for mystery shoppers, answer enquiries over phone / email

Sales Assistant

Kondo Tricot (2006 – 2007)

Attend customers at an independent fashion boutique in Fitzroy

EDUCATION

Coder Academy Aug 2017 – Feb 2018

Diploma of Information Technology

Oxford Brookes University

2004 - 2005

Study abroad programme (English Language and Literature/Letters)

Yasuda Women's College

2001 - 2003

Associate's Degree (Business, Commerce, Secretarial Management, English for Business)

ACHIEVEMENTS & INTERESTS

- 2017 ~: Regular Meetup tech events (Ruby and Rails, Junior Developers) goer
- 2017: Article contributions to an online travel magazine (TABIZINE Japanese) as a freelance writer
- 2013: Mother's Day Classic 4K
- 2008: Acquired PADI Open Water Diver licence
- 2002: Faculty representative of the study abroad programme at the University of Southern Queensland (USQ).